A Guide to the Richmond Renaissance Inc. Archives, 1956-1995
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library, Virginia Commonwealth University
Richmond Renaissance Inc. Archives, 1956-1995
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library, Virginia Commonwealth University
M 303
80 linear feet plus oversize materials, including posters and other large items.
Richmond Renaissance Inc. Archives
Administrative Information
Access
Materials in Series II, Box 6 are restricted.
Acquisition Information
The first donation from Richmond Renaissance Inc. Executive Director Clarence L. Townes, Jr. was made October 11, 1996, consisting of approximately 33 linear feet. A second donation from Richmond Renaissance Inc. occurred two years later, October 10, 1996, when the organization merged that month with the Central Richmond Association and Downtown Richmond Inc. This second donation consisted of 120 linear feet (many of which were oversize items, including posters and other large display materials).
Biographical/Historical Information
Richmond Renaissance Inc. is a non-profit, bi-racial, public-private corporation formed in 1981 to foster economic development in downtown Richmond. Its first major project was the 6th Street Marketplace, which opened in 1985. Revitalization of Richmond's historic Jackson Ward neighborhood and improvements to the city's downtown riverfront property were two other major initiatives in which Richmond Renaissance has played an active role. Richmond Renaissance has been involved with other projects, including the Jackson Center office building, the Belle Isle pedestrian bridge and Canal Walk, increased downtown parking, the Cultural Link Trolley Project, the Broad Street Task Force and numerous other efforts to foster economic development
The role and direction of Richmond Renaissance is overseen by its officers, many of whom are city officials, and a large board of directors (64 members in 1997). The board is comprised of prominent citizens, members of the business community, and various other city representatives. The Executive Committee manages the organization and includes members of the board, officers, and members of the Executive Staff. It is the Executive Staff which manages the day to day activities. The first Executive Director was J. Randall Evans, who served from October 1982 until December 1986. Clarence L. Townes, Jr. was the Deputy Director during that time. Townes then served as acting director from December 1986 to August 1987 when Robert E. Olson was named Executive Director. Townes continued as Deputy Director. In November 1991 Olson left to become Executive Director of the Virginia Biotechnology Research Park and Mr. Townes was named Executive Director.
In the fall of 1996, Richmond Renaissance Inc. merged with two other city organizations that had been promoting economic development in Richmond, the Central Richmond Association (CRA), begun in the early 1950s, and Downtown Richmond Inc. The merger was described as an attempt to unify "fund-raising efforts and to more effectively address Downtown issues." Townes continues in his position as Executive Director after the merger. Frances N. Johns, former director of CRA, was appointed Assistant Executive Director of Richmond Renaissance.
Scope and Content Information
The Richmond Renaissance Archives include correspondence, minutes, newspaper and journal clippings, various publications, reports, photographs, slides, and various promotional materials dating from 1956 through 1995. The bulk of the collection dates from 1982 through 1994 and focuses on Richmond Renaissance's activities to foster downtown Richmond revitalization. The collection documents the organization's involvement with a number of initiatives in the city, including the development of the city's riverfront properties, redevelopment of the downtown area, including Broad Street, and Jackson Ward neighborhood, and its planning, promotion and leadership in the development of the Sixth Street Marketplace.
Arrangement
Arrangement
The first deposit of the collection, consisting of about one third of the materials, was deposited to Special Collections and Archives (SCA) in transfile boxes labeled by subject (i.e. Jackson Ward, Sixth Street Marketplace). The collection was arranged to reflect this subject division, arranged topically by series and alphabetically therein. The second deposit of the collection has not been fully processed although it is inventoried and is accessible to researchers. Materials in this section of the archives will eventually be transferred to the appropriate collection series. Most of the original office folder headings have been maintained in the processing of this collection.
Organization
The collection is divided into seven series. Series I--Jackson Ward (n.d., 1964-1992) consists of materials relating to the redevelopment of Jackson Ward, a historic African-American Richmond neighborhood. This series also contains information on Broad Street, the Church Hill neighborhood, and other downtown revitalization initiatives. Series II--Riverfront (n.d., 1983-1991) is composed of material on various projects associated with the city's Riverfront area, including the Canal Walk, Belle Isle, and the James River Discovery Program. Series III--Sixth Street Marketplace (n.d., 1956-1986) documents the early years of the Sixth Street Marketplace project, from its planning stages to the first few years of its existence. Series IV--General Office Files and Correspondence (n.d., 1982-1989) contains the organization's general office file and correspondence. This series also contains material relating to projects other than those in the first three sections of the collection.
Series V--Miscellaneous Reports and Publications (n.d., 1980-1990) includes publications produced by the city, the state, the federal government, numerous organizations and publishers -- all relating to urban and regional planning. Series VI--Photographs, Slides, Video and Audio Tapes (n.d., 1984-1991) contains photographs, slides, and other media documenting many of the organization's endeavors -- including about three dozen large poster size placards used for presentations on Broad Street buildings and other redevelopment projects. The last series in the collection, Series VII, is made up of the second deposit of materials made by Richmond Renaissance, Inc. and includes materials found in the previous six sections of the collection. These materials date in range from 1969-1995 and will be placed in the appropriate sections of the collection in the future.
Series I--Jackson Ward (n.d., 1964-1992)
Series II--Riverfront (n.d., 1983-1991)
Series III--Sixth Street Marketplace (n.d., 1956-1986)
Series V--Miscellaneous Reports and Publications (n.d., 1980-1990)
Series VI--Photographs, Slides, Video and Audio Tapes (n.d., 1984-1991)
Series VII--Unprocessed Portion of Collection (n.d., 1969-1995)
Video and Audio Tapes
Richmond Renaissance; Nov. 20, 1992- No. 1, 2, 3
Slides of Richmond
Richmond Renaissance Slides
Jackson Ward Development Program Community Workshop No.1; Feb. 13, 1988
Moore BLAB TV Richmond: Still Making History; Apr. 25, 1987
Canal Walk Dedication
The John Marshal
R.R. No. 2
Richmond Renaissance: Jackson Ward to the James
Passages: Richmond Renaissance Master
6th Street Marketplace Minority Entrepreneur Development Program
Jackson Ward Development Workshop/Walking Tour Out Takes
Jackson Ward Development Workshop/Development Team Presentation
Sovran Bank/Richmond Presentation
American Security Bank Community Development Lending: Making A Difference
The Valentine Museum Jim Crow: The Search for New Southern Order
MEDC We're the Top
Richmond Renaissance; June 5, 1992
Richmond Redevelopment and Housing Authority
Public Relations Institute, Inc.
The Valentine Museum: In Bondage and Freedom
The Valentine Museum: Gilbert Hunt
Special Edition BLAB TV Jackson Center
Barrus Still Making History BLAB TV May 8, 1987
Tape (?)
Downtown Richmond Generic Version; Oct. 24, 1988
Commercial Real Estate Market Review; 1989
Burdick Group Projects: The Evolving Zoo
International Downtown Association:; Sep. 20, 1988 (Audio) Ida Version
Radio Smithsonian #931: The Painter of the American Nightmare, The Livable City (Audio)
Downtown Richmond Generic Version; Sep. 22, 1988 (Audio)
Memo to the Boss
Slides
Morgan Stanley Presentation; Mar, 18, 1988
Olson, Bob
Evans: Short History
Downtown Richmond; 1988
Richmond Renaissance; Dec. 1987
Posters
Isn't It Time We Showed As Much Devotion to Richmond's Future as Have The Past
Metropolitan Visitor Center
Richmond Bumper Sticker
Richmond Still Making History (2)
Richmond Still Making History: T-shirts (3)
Floor Plan Of Richmond Visitor Center
Floor Plan: Belle Isle Environmental Education Center
The Headman Frank Padget
Our New Cultural Link Trolley Will Send You For a Loop
Bermuda Tourism Strategic Planning Process
Aerial View of Jackson Ward (2 color, 2 black and white)
Facade Renovation Project
Broad Street Old and Historic District
Map of Richmond
Thermostat Company: Robert Shaw
Richmond XXI: The Right Place...The Right Time
Photo Survey of Belle Isle
Map of Culture Link Trolley Stops
Link Schedule Singage
Richmond Still Making History Baseball Cap
Directional Signage (2)
Richmond Still Making History Billboard (2)
Richmond Still Making History Directional Signage
Track Trolley
Flags Design
Jackson Centre (Rendering)
Single Family Residential Rehabilitation
Belle Isle Paths and Walkways
Mid-rise Multi- Family New Construction (Rendering)
Floor Plan Single Family Infill New Construction (Rendering)
Mid and High Rise New Construction
Belle Isle Study: Map (2)
Canal Walk Brown's Island Improvement (2)
Downtown
Concepts of Proposed Vehicular Access (2)
Bridge Across James River South Bank of Belle Isle
Belle Isle
History of Jackson Ward
Richmond Apparel
Belle Isle Pedestrian Bridge Plan
Belle Isle History
James River and Kanawha Canal
Haxall Canal Location
Pedestrian Bridge to Belle Isle and Belle Isle Design (reverse side)
Broad Street Facades
Broad Street Facade Renovation Project Area
Jackson Ward Map
Foushee Street to First- North Side
Adams to Foushee- South Side
Adams to Foushee- North Side
Foushee to First- South Side
Eighth to Ninth- North Side
Eighth to Ninth- South Side
Seventh to Eighth- South Side
Third to Fourth- South Side
Third to Fourth-North Side
Second to Third- South Side
Second to Third- North Side
Fourth to Fifth- South Side
Proposed Gateway and Visitor Center (Broad and Adams)
James River and Kanawha Walk
Belle Isle Public Parking
The Link: Linking History To The Future
Schedule: Metropolitan Visitor Information Center (2)
Prototypical Rendering of MCV
Multi-Family Infill New Construction
Contents List
- Series I--Jackson Ward 1964-1992
  - ABC Hearing 1991 (Box 1)
  - Addition to Processing Handbook, Elderly Housing 1990 (Box 1)
  - Arican American Heritage Development Plan 1991 (Box 1)
  - Architechts-James River Chapter 1991 (Box 1)
  - Broad/Grace/2nd Street Conservation Area 1990 (Box 1)
  - Broad/Grace/2nd Street Conservation Ordinance 1991 (Box 1)
  - Broad/Grace St. Retail (1 of 2) 1987-1989 (Box 1)
  - Broad/Grace St. Retail (2 of 2) 1987-1989 (Box 1)
  - Broad Street and Downtown Redevelopment Plan (2 of 4) (Box 1)
  - Broad Street and Downtown Redevelopment Plan (3 of 4) 1990 (Box 1)
  - Broad Street and Downtown Redevelopment Plan (4 of 4) 1990 (Box 1)
  - Business News Related to Downtown Core 1983-1988 (Box 1)
  - Business Permits, Regulation, Taxes-Guide, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Business Related Brochures (Box 1)
  - Central Wards Planning Study (1 of 2) 1976 (Box 1)
  - Central Wards Planning Study (2 of 2) 1976 (Box 1)
  - Christmas in April-A Guide for Communities 1989 (Box 1)
  - Church Hill (1 of 2) 1982-1986 (Box 1)
  - Church Hill (2 of 2) 1982-1986 (Box 1)
  - Citizen's Report-A strategic Plan for Richmond's Future Tomorrow, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Coaxum, Pamela-Miscellaneous Notes and Corresondence 1991 (Box 1)
  - Commercial Rehab Loan 1991 (Box 1)
  - Commercial Rehab Loan Program 1991 (Box 1)
  - Commercial Rehabilitation Loan Program (Box 1)
  - Referrals (Marshall St) (Box 1)
  - 5-9 W. Broad Street (Box 1)
  - 101-109 E. Broad Street 1991 (Box 1)
  - 122 W. Leigh Street 1991 (Box 1)
  - 128-122 W. Broad Street 1991 (Box 1)
  - 200-202 E. Broad Street (1 of 2) 1991 (Box 1)
  - 200-202 E. Broad Street (2 of 2) (Box 1)
  - 207 Clay Steet (Box 1)
  - 213 Clay Street 1991 (Box 1)
  - 414-424 N. 2nd Street (Box 1)
  - 516 N. 2nd Street 1991 (Box 1)
  - 526 N. 2nd Street 1991 (Box 1)
  - 532-528 2nd Steet 1990 (Box 1)
  - 532-528 2nd Street 1990 (Box 1)
  - 2nd Street ABC Store (1 of 2) 1991 (Box 1)
  - Community Investments Conference 1991 (Box 1)
  - Deeds-Property Transfers (Box 1)
  - Development Potential-Downtown Richmond-Urban Land Institute Report Heritage Project (2 of 4) 1991 (Box 1)
  - Downtown Retail Market Analysis 1986, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Downtown Development Team 1991 (Box 1)
  - Facade Estimates 1989, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Fan/West End n.d. (Box 1)
  - Forms, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Greater Richmond Community Foundation-Grant Program 1991 (Box 1)
  - Hippodrome Theatre (Box 2)
  - Historic Streetcar Study 1984 (Box 2)
  - Housing and Community Service Directory 1989 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Center Dedication (1 of 3) 1992 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Center Dedication (2 of 3) 1992 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Center Dedication (3 of 3) 1992 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Center Leasing, 1989-1990, undated (Box 2)
  - Jackson Center Leasing Committee (photograph of Jackson Center removed; placed in Series VI) (Box 2)
  - Jackson Center Mailing List n.d. (Box 2)
  - Jackson Center Ground breaking (1 of 2) (photograph of Jackson Center removed; placed in Series VI) 1991 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Center Ground breaking (2 of 2) 1991 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Place-Building Evaluation (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward-Building New Traditions (brochure) (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Business and Property Owners 1990 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Business Association (1 of 4) 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Business Association (2 of 4) 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Business Association (3 of 4) 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Business Association (4 of 4) 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Business Association-Board Meetings (1 of 3) 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Business Association-Board Meetings (2 of 3) 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Business Association-Board Meetings (3 of 3) 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Flags 1991 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Maps (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Newsletter (The Vision) (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Track Trash Receptacles 1991 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Vision 2000 1988 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Vision 2000 Correspondence, Minutes 1989-1991 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Vision 2000-Misc. Correspondence, n.d. 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Vision 2000 (Printed Documents from a Computer Disc) Minutes, Reports, Miscellaneous (1 of 2) 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Vision 2000 (Printed Documents from a Computer Disc) Minutes, Reports, Miscellaneous (2 of 2) 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward 2000, Richmond, Virginia-Technical Report May 1988 (Box 2)
  - Jackson Ward Vision 2000, Technical Report 1988 (Box 2)
  - James River and Kanawha Canal (brochure), n.d. (Box 2)
  - Landmark and Historic Places-2nd Street and African-American Heritage Project 1991 (Box 3)
  - Lender (Investors Financial) 1990 (Box 3)
  - Media (Box 3)
  - Median Income Projection 1986 (Box 3)
  - National Coalition of 100 Black Women Inc. 1991 (Box 3)
  - National Historic Resistor-African-American Heritage Project 1991 (Box 3)
  - National Main St. Center-Reorganization and Motivation (Box 3)
  - News Articles on the Revitalization of Richmond (1 of 2) 1982-1986 (Box 3)
  - News Articles on the Revitalization of Richmond (2 of 2) 1982-1986 (Box 3)
  - Northside 1980-1989 (Box 3)
  - Notes-Miscellaneous Material (Box 3)
  - Policy and Development Committee Lists (Box 3)
  - Processing Handbook, Elderly Housing 1985 (Box 3)
  - Processing Handbook, Elderly Housing Appendixes 1985 (Box 3)
  - Rental Information 1991 (Box 3)
  - Richmond and Virginia Maps (1 of 2) (Box 3)
  - Richmond and Virginia Maps (2 of 2) (Box 3)
  - Richmond Community Development Corporation Projects 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Richmond Dairy (Box 3)
  - Richmond Economic Development 1991 (Box 3)
  - Richmond First Club 1990 (Box 3)
  - Richmond Regional Planning District Commission (1 of 2) 1986 (Box 3)
  - Richmond Regional Planning District Commission (2 of 2) 1986 (Box 3)
  - Richmond Renaissance Address Labels (printed from a RR computer disc) (Box 3)
  - Richmond Renaissance, Inc.-Business (1 of 3) 1982-1990 (Box 3)
  - Richmond Renaissance, Inc.-Business (2 of 3) 1982-1990 (Box 3)
  - Richmond Renaissance, Inc.-Business-(3 of 3) 1982-1990 (Box 3)
  - Richmond Renaissance Education Committee, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Riverfront Development (1 of 2) (Box 3)
  - Riverfront Development (2 of 2) (Box 3)
  - Section 8 Income Limits (Box 4)
  - Second Street Business District-Revitalization 1983 (Box 4)
  - Second Street Commercial Area 1981 (Box 4)
  - Second Street Commercial Revitalization 1981 (Box 4)
  - Secretary of Interior-Standards for Rehab. 1983 (Box 4)
  - Historic Preservation Consultants 1989 (Box 4)
  - Shockoe Slip and Bottom-News clippings (1 of 3) 1975-1989 (Box 4)
  - Shockoe Slip and Bottom-News clippings (2 of 3) 1975-1989 (Box 4)
  - Shockoe Slip and Bottom-News clippings (3 of 3) 1975-1989 (Box 4)
  - Southern Gateway-Dept. of Planning and Community Development 1986 (Box 4)
  - Southwest Downtown 1984-1996 (Box 4)
  - State of City Report 1989 (Box 4)
  - Street Improvements, n.d. (Box 4)
  - Street Car Study (Box 4)
  - Summary-Housing Action Plan, n.d. (Box 4)
  - Third Street Project 1982 (Box 4)
  - Valentine Museum 1989 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Alcholic Beverage Control-Board Regulations 1989, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Association Fund Raising Executives 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Virginia College Savings Bond Program-brochure (Box 4)
  - Virginia Legislation Directories 1986 (Box 4)
  - Vision 2000 Community Loan 1991 (Box 4)
  - Vision 2000 Projects, n.d. (Box 4)
  - Zoning-District Map 1978 through October 9, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Exhibit Material, oversized (Box 4)
  - Richmond Renaissance Newsletter, oversized (Box 4)
  - Brook Crossing Commercial Center, Revitalization Plan, Richmond Revitalization Program, VCU School of Community and Public Affairs, Center for Public Affairs, Dept. of Urban Studies and Planning 1982 (Box 5)
  - Brook Crossing Commercial Center, Existing Conditions, Richmond Revitalization Program, VCU School of Community and Public Affairs, Center for Public Affairs, Dept. of Urban Studies and Planning 1982 (Box 5)
  - Brook Crossing COmmercial Center, Neighborhood Profile, Richmond Revitalization Program, VCU School of Community and Public Affairs, Center for Public Affairs, Dept. of Urban Studies and Planning 1982 (Box 5)
  - City of Richmond Minority Business and Tenant Opportunity Program, 6th Street Market, n.d. (Box 5)
  - City of Richmond Neighborhood Statistics, 1980 Census 1985 (Box 5)
  - City-Wide Survey of Attitudes and Opinions Regarding Downtown, Southeastern Institute of Research, Inc. (Box 5)
  - Downtown Plan 1st Draft 1984 (Box 5)
  - Expansion/Modernization Byrd International Airport (Box 5)
  - Gallery Plaza, An Office/Rental/Residential Project-Richmond, Va(Masonic Temple on Broad) (Box 5)
  - CF Associates, Hanson Associates, n.d. (Box 5)
  - Housing Action Plan, Richmond, Virginia, n.d. (Box 5)
  - Master Plan of Land Us, Community Facilities and Trafficway Planning Commission City of Richmond, Virginia 1964 (Box 5)
  - National Development Council-Economic Development Financing 1985 (Box 5)
  - National Development Council-Financing Case Study Manual 1985 (Box 5)
  - National Register of Historic Places Inventory--Nomination Form-Jackson Ward July 30, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Old and Historic Districts 1985, Commission of Architectural Review, Chapter 17, Richmond City Code 1985 (Box 5)
  - A Proposed Strategy for Organizing, Staffing and Funding a Renaissance in Tourism and Convention Development in the Richmond, Virginia Area, prepared for Richmond Renaissance Corporation, Dr. John D. Hunt, Project Leader, Washington, D.C. September 15, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Project 1 Area Parking Study Wilbur Smith and Associates 1983 (Box 5)
  - Revitalization Plan for the Second Street Business District Area Richmond, Virginia 1983 (Box 5)
  - Shockoe Bottom Revitalization Plan-Richmond Revitalization Program, VCU School of Community and Public Affairs, Center for Public Affairs, Dept. of Urban Studies and Planning 1982 (Box 5)
  - Strategy for Action for Downtown Richmond, n.d. 1976-2000 (Box 5)
  - Summary-Findings of Broad/Grace Street Retail District Analysis 1986 (Box 5)
  - Summary of Major Features of the Comprehensive Zoning Ordinance 1978 (Box 5)
  - Summary of RRHA/City Downtown Housing Proposal (Box 5)
  - Third and Clay Building Devco Inc. Draft, n.d. (Box 5)
  - Transit Development Program for the Richmond Urbanized Area 1990-1994 Greater Richmond Transit Company 1989 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Business Resource Directory 1983 (Box 5)
- Series II--Riverfront, n.d. 1983-1991
  - Six Binders with Receipts of Canal Walk Bricks, Including Names A-Z 1986-1987 (Box 6)
    Individuals, organizations, and businesses could purchase a brick inscribed with the name of their choice on it. Location choices for bricks included: 12th Street between Main and Canal Streets; Brown's Island Landing Side of Brown's Island/7th Street Bridge; 7th street Side of Brown's Island/7th Street Bridge; Kanawha Plaza. Because some receipts include credit card numbers of individuals, access to these binders is restricted.
  - Belle Isle Bridge II1986, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Bridge-Correspondence, Reports, Notes, n.d. 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Bridge-Correspondence, Reports, Notes, n.d. 1989-1991 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Bridge-Funding-City of Richmond 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Bridge-Funding-Commonwealth of Virginia 1986-1987 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Bridge-Funding-Correspondence, Notes Miscellaneous 1986-1987 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Dedication- Belle Isle: A Historic Treasure-Wm. Byrd Branch, APVA 1991 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Dedication-Correspondence, Notes, Drawings, Miscellaneous 1991 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Pedestrian Bridge-Correspondence, Notes Miscellaneous 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Pedestrian Bridge-Correspondence, Notes 1987-1991 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Pedestrian Bridge-Permits, Clearances 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Pedestrian Bridge-Pier Bridge-Correspondence, Notes, Estimates 1986 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Pedestrian Bridge-Press Package 1991 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Railway Bridge/Vehicular Access Bridge 1985-1987 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Railway Bridge/Vehicular Access Bridge 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Vehicular Access Bridge, n.d. 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Vehicular Access Bridge-Correspondence, Notes includes City of Richmond Bid Information 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Vehicular Access Bridge-Feasibility Study 1987 (Box 7)
  - Belle Isle Whitman, Requardt and Associates Engineers 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Brick Campaign 1985-1989 (Box 7)
  - Brick Correspondence 1986-1989 (Box 7)
  - Brick Orders-Arts Council 1987-1989 (Box 8)
  - Brick Orders-Astoria Beneficial Club 1986-1988 (Box 8)
  - Brick Orders-Best Products 1986-1988 (Box 8)
  - Brick Orders-Best Products 1988 (Box 8)
  - Brick Orders-Fire Fighters, NASA, Police 1987 (Box 8)
  - Brick Orders-Memorial Title Bricks; Miscellaneous Special Orders 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Brick Orders-Virginia Power 1988 (Box 8)
  - Brick Program-Miscellaneous Notes, Accounting, n.d. 1986-1988 (Box 8)
  - Buy a Block in Downtown Richmond-Ceremony 1987 (Box 8)